Postcards
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Postcards, 2.1.7
  - London, England, circa 1922; 12 (Box 1599)
    - LONDON. REGENT STREET.- This famous street of beautiful shops commences at Pall Mall, and runs northwards through Piccadilly Circus and Oxford Circus., 20-verso
    - Oxford Street, London., 21
    - LONDON. OXFORD STREET. -The heart of London shopping., 21-verso
    - The Marble Arch, London., 22
    - LONDON. THE MARBLE ARCH. -The main north-west entry into Hyde Park. Park Lane, Bayswater Road, and Oxford Street meet here., 22-verso
    - Triumphal Arch, Constitution Hill, London., 23
    - LONDON. THE DECIMUS BURION ARCH, at the top of Constitution Hill, surmointed by a quadriga, by Captain Adrian Jones, depicting Peace with Victory., 23-verso
    - The Tower Bridge, London., 24
    - LONDON. THE TOWER BRIDGE. -The foundation-stone was laid by His late Majesty Edward VII, then Prince of Wales, in 1886, The centre span consists of two bascules, which are raised to allow the passage of large steamers, as seen in the picture., 24-verso
    - The Tower of London., 25
    - LONDON. THE TOWER OF LONDON. -The Tower is of great historic interest, and contains the Crown Jewels, as well as a wonderful collection of armour of all periods., 25-verso
  - France, circa 1922; 13 (Box 1599)
    - Dom Sud [church building in France], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - Hyeres. - La Cueillette des Marguerites. - LL. [Women picking daisies], 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - Marseille. N. -D. de la Garde vue du Vieux Port. [Guard for the Old Port] Editon speciale de la Basilique. [Special edition of the Basilica], 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - XXXVI. - Marseillle. - Notre-Dame de la Garde. Edition Speciale de la Basilique. [Special edition of the Basilica], 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
    - NICE - Vue G n rale vers Cimiez et l'Observatoire - V. M. [View of Cimiez district of Nice and the Observatory], 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
    - NICE - Le March aux L gumes - V. M. [The Vegetable Market], 6
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 6-verso
    - Monte-Carlo. - Casino et Jardins [Casino and Gardens], 7
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 7-verso
    - Monte-Carlo. - Le Th tre et les Terrasses [The Theatre and the Terraces], 8
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 8-verso
    - Place de la Concorde, [a major public square in Paris, France], 9
    - Joyeus No l et Hereuse Ann e [Merry Christmas and Happy New Year] - Daleleaunagey [?], 9-verso
    - Iles de L rins. - Ile Sainte-Marguerite. - Le Fort. - LL. [Lerins Islands, Saint Margaret Island, Fort Royal], 10
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 10-verso
    - Hy res. - Panorama de la Ville Haute. - Panorama of the High Town. - LL., 11
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 11-verso
  - Cannes, France, circa 1922; 14 (Box 1599)
    - CANNES. Vue Generale prise du Mt. Chevalier [General view taken from Mount Knight]. ND. Phot., 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - CANNES. - Le Mont chevalier [Mount Knight]. - LL., 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - CANNES. - L'H tel Carlton [Carlton Hotel]. - LL., 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - CANNES. - La Croisette et le Mont Chevalier [The Croisette walkway and Mount Knight]. - LL., 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
    - CANNES. - La Croisette et Panorama sur L'Est rel [Panorama of the Croisette walkway and the Esterel mountains in France]. - LL., 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
  Box 1600
- Postcards, 2.1.7
  - Menton, France, circa 1922; 1 (Box 1600)
    - MENTON. - Grimaldi, Vue sur le Restaurant des Grottes et le Casino. Frontiere Franco-Italienne.[View of the restaurants, caves, and casinos.] ND. Phot., 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - MENTON. - Le Port et le Quai, The Wharf and the Quay, 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - MENTON. Les Jardins du Care, le Casino Municipal et les Montagnes de Ste. Agn s. [The gardens of Carei, the Municipal Casino, and the mountains of St. Agnes] ND. Phot., 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - MENTON (Alpes-Maritimes) - Excelsior-Hotel, 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
  - Paris, France, circa 1922; 2 (Box 1600)
    - HOTEL LOUVOIS - Square Louvois - PARIS, 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - PARIS - Port de la Tournelle et Abside Notre-Dame C. M. [Port Tournelle road and the apse of Notre-Dame], 2
    - Tous les pays trangers n'acceptent pas la correspondance au recto (Se renseigner la Poste) [All other countries do not accept correspondence on the front. Inquire at the post office.], 2-verso
    - PARIS (8e arrt.) L'Arc de Triomphe de l'Etoile. Hauteur 49m,50 281 marches Sur ses 4 faces: Le D part de Rude, La R sistance d' tex La Paix d' tex Le Triomphe de Cortot C. M. [The Arc de Triomphe. Height 49m, 50,281 steps on its four sides.], 3
    - Tous les pays trangers n'acceptent pas la correspondance au recto (Se renseigner la Poste) [All other countries do not accept correspondence on the front. Inquire at the post office.], 3-verso
    - PARIS - glise Notre Dame Commenc e en 1163 et termin e en 1230. La premi re pierre fut pos e par le pape Alexandre III et le roi Louis VII [Notre Dame began in 1163 and ended in 1230. The first stone was laid by Pope Alexander III and King Louis VII.]C. M., 4
    - Tous les pays trangers n'acceptent pas la correspondance au recto (Se renseigner la Poste) [All other countries do not accept correspondence on the front. Inquire at the post office.], 4-verso
    - PARIS- Le Pont Royal er le Pavillon de Flore A.P. The Royal Bridge and the Pavillon de Flore., 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
    - PARIS. La Tour Saint-Jaques. [The tower of Saint Jaques] - LL., 6
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 6-verso
    - PARIS - Op ra et la Station M tro A.P. Opera House and Metropolitain Railway Station, 7
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 7-verso
    - PARIS. - La Tour Eiffel. - LL. [Eiffel Tower], 8
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 8-verso
    - PARIS. - La Place de la Concorde et la Seine [A major square in Paris by the Seine River] - LL., 9
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 9-verso
    - PARIS. - Le Nouveau Louvre. - The New Louvre., 10
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 10-verso
    - PARIS (8e arrt) - La Rue Royale et la Madeleine C. M., 11
    - Tous les pays trangers n'acceptent pas la correspondance au recto (Se renseigner la Poste) [All other countries do not accept correspondence on the front. Inquire at the post office.], 11-verso
    - PARIS - La Rue Castiglione et la Colonne Vend me A.P. Castiglione Street and the Vendome Column, 12
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 12-verso
    - PARIS (8e arrt.) L'Arc de Triomphe de l'Etoile. Hauteur 49m,50 281 marches Sur ses 4 faces: Le D part de Rude, La R sistance d' tex La Paix d' tex Le Triomphe de Cortot C. M. [The Arc de Triomphe. Height 49m, 50,281 steps on its four sides.], 13
    - Tous les pays trangers n'acceptent pas la correspondance au recto (Se renseigner la Poste) [All other countries do not accept correspondence on the front. Inquire at the post office.], 13-verso
  - Reims Cathedral, France, circa 1922; 3 (Box 1600)
    - REIMS. - La Cath drale incendi e par les Allemands le 9 Septembre 1914. The Cathedral burnt by the Germans on the 19th September 1914., 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - REIMS avant la Grande Guerre La Cath drale. The Cathedral before the War., 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - REIMS dans les Ruines apr s la Retraite des Allemands. [Remis in ruins after the retreat of the Germans] La Cath drale travers les Ruines, The Cathedral among the Ruins., 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - REIMS dans les Ruines apr s la Retraite des Allemands. [Remis in ruins after the retreat of the Germans] La Cath drale - The Cathedral, 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
  - Sospel, France, circa 1922; 4 (Box 1600)
    - ENV. DE MENTON. - Sospel. - Le Pont de la Loge. [The bridge to the Island Lodge] LL., 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - SOSPEL (Alpes-Maritimes). - Le vieux Pont. [The Old Bridge in Sospel, France], 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - SOSPEL (Alpes-Marit.). - Portail de l'ancien Ch teau. F. I [Gateway to the old castle in Sospel, France], 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - SOSPEL (Alpes-Maritimes). - Le Pont Vieux [People standing on the Old Bridge in Sospel, France], 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
    - SOSPEL (Alpes-Marit.). Vue sur le Vieux Pont et les Montagnes d'Italie F. L. [View of the Old Bridge and the Mountains of Italy in Sospel, France.], 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
    - SOSPEL (Alpes-Maritimes). - Le vieux Pont. [The Old Bridge in Sospel, France], 6
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 6-verso
  - Germany, circa 1922; 5 (Box 1600)
    - [German village, Bacharach, with river and mountains in background], 1
    - Bacharach ,mit Ruine Stahleck hat sich seinen mittelalterlichen malerischen Charakter durch die Stadtmauern erhalten und ist ber hmt durch seinen Weinbau. [Bacharach, with Stahleck Castle ruins, has medieval picturesque character obtained by the city walls and is famous for its wine.], 1-verso
    - [German village, Bacharach, with river and mountains in background], 2
    - Bacharach ,mit Ruine Stahleck hat sich seinen mittelalterlichen malerischen Charakter durch die Stadtmauern erhalten und ist ber hmt durch seinen Weinbau. [Bacharach, with Stahleck Castle ruins, has medieval picturesque character obtained by the city walls and is famous for its wine.], 2-verso
    - Schwarzwald-Hotel, Titisee, 860 m. M., 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - R desheim., 4
    - R desheim. Die Wahrzelchen des ber hmten Weinst dtchens sind der mittelalterliche viereckige Alderturm und die Im 14. Jahrh. Erbaute kath, Kirche. Auf der Hohe das Nationaldenkmal. [The famous landmark wine town with medieval square tower and the 14th Alder Built in century Catholic Church. On the High National Monument.], 4-verso
    - [Castle on a river], 5
    - Burg Katz mit Blick auf St. Goar und Ruine Rheinfels. Herrlicher Ausblick auf das Rheintal Nach der Restaurierung der fr heren Ruine befindet sich die Burg im Besitz des Landrats Berg. [Katz Castle overlooking St. Goar and the Rhine Castle ruins. Magnificent views of the Rhine valley after the restoration of the ruins of the former castle located in the district of the Besitz mountain.], 5-verso
    - Marksbug., 6
    - DIE MARKSBURG von der Rheinseite gesehen, mit der alten Kirche und dem Kriegerdenkmal in Braubach, 150 m ber dem Rheinspiegel, die einzige erhaltene Burg am Rhein. Bis 1866 nassauisches Staatsgef ngnis, ist sie jetzt im besitz des Vereins zur Erhaltung deutschei Burgen. [The Marksburg Castle seen from the side of the Rhine, with the old church and the war memorial in Braubach, 150 meters above the Rhine River. It is the only preserved castle on the Rhine. Nassovian state prison until 1866, it is now in the possession of the Association for the Preservation of castles.], 6-verso
    - Marksburg., 7
    - DIE MARKSBURG von der Rheinseite gesehen, mit der alten Kirche und dem Kriegerdenkmal in Braubach, 150 m ber dem Rheinspiegel, die einzige erhaltene Burg am Rhein. Bis 1866 nassauisches Staatsgef ngnis, ist sie jetzt im besitz des Vereins zur Erhaltung deutschei Burgen. [The Marksburg Castle seen from the side of the Rhine, with the old church and the war memorial in Braubach, 150 meters above the Rhine River. It is the only preserved castle on the Rhine. Nassovian state prison until 1866, it is now in the possession of the Association for the Preservation of castles.], 7-verso
    - Bad Homburg v. d. H. Parkpartie, 8
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 8-verso
    - Bad Homburg v. d. H. Parkpartie, 9
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 9-verso
    - TODTNAU, H henluftkurort, Bad, Schwarzwald, 10
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 10-verso
    - Die Loreley [The Lorelei rock on the Rhine], 11
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 11-verso
    - [Night view of the city of Cologne, Germany, located on the Rhine River], 12
    - COELN: Panorama bei Nacht [Panorama at night], 12-verso
    - [Night view of the city of Cologne, Germany, located on the Rhine River], 13
    - COELN: Panorama bei Nacht [Panorama at night], 13-verso
  - Germany (navy), undated; 6 (Box 1600)
    - Englische Ubootsflottille an der flandrischen K ste. 1729 Verl. Finke Wilhelmshaven [English submarine on the coast of Flanders.], 1
    - English submarines on Flouder coast., 1-verso
    - H. M. Submarine E4, 2
    - To be returned to W. G. Cleaver. Leornard William Smith, Leading Telegraphist, Official Number J9412, 2-verso
    - DI Last but not Least [Group of German sailors], 3
    - To be returned to W. G. Cleaver. (Clever is behind [?] at right). Mr. Cleaver, Submarine DI., 3-verso
  - Berlin, Germany, circa 1922; 7 (Box 1600)
    - BERLIN. Reichstag-Geb ude. [The Reichtag building], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - BERLIN. Gendarmenmarkt mit Schauspielhaus und Franz sische Kirche. [Gendarmenmarkt square, Schauspielhaus theater and French Church.], 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - BERLIN. Schlo und National-Denkmal. [Palace and National Monument], 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - BERLIN. Brandenburger-Tor und Reichstag-Geb ude. [Brandenburg Gate and Reichstag Building], 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
    - Berlin. Jannowitzbr cke. [Railway station], 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
    - BERLIN. Schlo und National-Denkmal. Frederick Great [?] [Palace and National Monument], 6
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 6-verso
    - BERLIN. Schlo und Schlo r cke. [Bridge and buildings in Germany], 7
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 7-verso
    - BERLIN. Oberbaumbr cke. [Oberbaum Bridge], 8
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 8-verso
    - Berlin. Lustgarten u. Schloss [Pleasure Garden, manor in the background], 9
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 9-verso
    - BERLIN. Gendarmenmarkt mit Schauspielhaus und Franz sische Kirche. [Gendarmenmarkt square, Schauspielhaus theater and French Church.], 10
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 10-verso
    - Berlin. Sieges-Allee [Victory Avenue], 11
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 11-verso
    - BERLIN. Schlo platz. [Castle Square], 12
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 12-verso
    - BERLIN. Bismarckdenkmal und Siegess ule. [Bismark Memorial and Victory Column], 13
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 13-verso
    - BERLIN. Oberbaumbr cke. [Oberbaum Bridge], 14
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 14-verso
    - BERLIN. Schauspielhaus. [Schauspielhaus theater], 15
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 15-verso
    - BERLIN. Pariser-Platz und Brandenburger-Tor. [Paris Square and The Brandenburg Gate], 16
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 16-verso
    - [Group of men and women in an automobile in Berlin with sign in front of Hotel Bauer], 17
    - Berlin Aug[ust] 3rd, 1922. Unter den Linden. ["Under the linden (lime) trees"; a boulevard in the Mitte district of Berlin], 17-verso
    - [Group of men and women in large automobile in Berlin with sign and driver], 18
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 18-verso
    - [Group of men and women in Berlin in a large automobile with sign and driver] [Duplicate], 19
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 19-verso
    - [Group of men and women in Berlin in a large automobile with sign and driver] [Duplicate], 20
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 20-verso
  - Dresden, Germany, circa 1922; 8 (Box 1600)
    - Dresden - Zwinger. [German palace], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - Dresden. Kath. Kirche - Opernhaus [Catholic Church - Opera House], 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - HOTEL BELLEVUE, DRESDEN. Terrasse und Veranda, 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - [View of a Dresden cathedral and opera house on a river], 4
    - DRESDEN, 4-verso
  - Frankfurt, Germany, circa 1922; 9 (Box 1600)
    - Frankfurt a. M., R merberg. [Central square of Frankfurt], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - Frankfurt a. M. Zeil. [Popular shopping street], 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - Frankfurt a. M. Schauspielhaus. [Schauspielhaus theater], 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - Frankfurt a. M., Rothschildhaus, B rnestra e 26 [Rothschild House], 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
    - Frankfurt a. M., Hauptwache, Schillerplatz, Blick in die Zeil [Main guard building, Schiller Square, looking at Zeil, shopping district], 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
    - Frankfurt a. M., Goethehaus, Sr. Hirschgraben 23 (16 Jahrh.) [Goethe House, sixteenth century], 6
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 6-verso
    - Frankfurt a. M. Universitat [University in Frankfurt], 7
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 7-verso
    - Frankfurt a. M, Am R merberg, 8
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 8-verso
    - Frankfurt a. M. R mer, 9
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 9-verso
    - Frankfurt a. M. Goethehaus Sr. Hirschgraben 23 (16. Jahrh.) [Goethe House, sixteenth century], 10
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 10-verso
    - Frankfurt a. M., Alte H user am R mer (Haus Frauenstein, Salzhaus) [Old houses at Romer. (Stone house, Salt house)], 11
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 11-verso
    - Frankfurt a. M., Haus Wannebach. [Courtyard in Frankfurt], 12
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 12-verso
  - Heidelberg, Germany, circa 1922; 10 (Box 1600)
    - [View of Heidelberg], 1
    - Heidelberg vom Philosophenweg gesehen bei Mondschein. [Heidelberg seen from the Philosophers walk in the moonlight.], 1-verso
    - [Drawing of people and wagon on a bridge to Heildelberg], 2
    - Heidelberg Die alte Nekarbr cke mit Blick auf das Schlo. [Castle overlooking the old Neckar Bridge.], 2-verso
    - [View of Heidelberg Castle through the woods], 3
    - Schlo Heidelberg. [Heidelberg Castle], 3-verso
    - [Medieval architecture], 4
    - Heidelberg. Der Erker am Bibliotheksbau [The library building], 4-verso
    - [Heildelberg courtyard], 5
    - Heidelberg. Der Schlosshof [Courtyard], 5-verso
    - [Heildelberg courtyard], 6
    - Heidelberg. Der Schlosshof [Courtyard], 6-verso
    - [Bridge near Hiedelberg], 7
    - Heidelberg Die alte Nekarbr cke [The old Neckar Bridge.], 7-verso
  - Munich, Germany, circa 1922; 11 (Box 1600)
    - M nchen Bahnhofplatz [Station Square], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - [Classical building and schulpture], 2
    - M nchen Bavaria mit Ruhmeshalle [Hall of Fame in Bavaria, Munich], 2-verso
    - M nchen Karlstor [One of the four main gates of the medieval city wall], 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - COELN: Rathaus mit Glockenspiel. [New city hall], 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
    - [Karlstor, one of the main gates of the medieval city wall], 5
    - M nchen, Karlstor mit Neuhausertrase [Kalstor gate in Neuhauser Strasse], 5-verso
    - [Man and woman standing in front of the Wittelsbach Fountain], 6
    - M nchen, Wittelsbacherbrunnen [Whittelsbach Fountain], 6-verso
    - [Munich Palace of Justice, street and cable cars], 7
    - M nchen, Justizpalast [Palace of Justice], 7-verso
    - [Street going into Munich from a bridge], 8
    - M nchen, Blick vom Maximilianeum [View from Maximailianeum, palatial building], 8-verso
    - [Farm, women and logs in the foreground], 9
    - Schwarzwald. Bauernhof bei Neu-Eck [Farm at New Corner], 9-verso
  - Munich, Germany (Passion Play), 1922; 12 (Box 1600)
    - TRAUT phot. [Jesus], 1
    - Passionsspiele O. - Ammergau 1922. Nr. 1 Jesus - Anton Lang. [Passion play], 1-verso
    - [Jesus at Last Supper], 2
    - Passionsspiele O. - Ammergau 1922. Nr. 57 Jesus beim Abendmahle [Passion play, Jesus at the Last Supper], 2-verso
    - [Jesus at Last Supper], 3
    - Passionsspiele O. - Ammergau 1922. Nr. 57 Jesus beim Abendmahle [Passion play, Jesus at the Last Supper], 3-verso
    - [Scene of 4 shepards near Jerusalem], 4
    - Passionsspiele O. - Ammergau 1922. Nr. 54 Gang nach Jerusalem [Passion play, passage to Jerusalem], 4-verso
    - [Group of shepards walking to Jerusalem], 5
    - Passionsspiele O. - Ammergau 1922. Nr. 52 Gang nach Jerusalem [Passion play, passage to Jerusalem], 5-verso
    - [Group of Shepards, Jesus weeping over Jerusalem], 6
    - Passionsspiele O. - Ammergau 1922. Nr. 53 Jesus weint ber Jerusalem [Jesus weeps over Jerusalem], 6-verso
    - [Jesus in front of Pilate], 7
    - Passionsspiele O. - Ammergau 1922. Nr. 49 Jesus vor Pilatus. [Jesus before Pilate], 7-verso
    - [Jesus on the Mount of Olives], 8
    - Passionsspiele O. - Ammergau 1922. Nr. 56 Jesus am Oelberg [Jesus on the Mount of Olives], 8-verso
    - [Wailing women], 9
    - Passionsspiele O. - Ammergau 1922. Nr. 55 Die klagenden Frauen. The wailing women], 9-verso
    - [Judas before the Sanhedrin], 10
    - Passionsspiele O. - Ammergau 1922. Nr. 47 Judas vor dem Synedrium [Jesus before the Sanhedrin], 10-verso
    - [After the denial], 11
    - Passionsspiele O. - Ammergau 1922. Nr. 48 Begegnung nach der Verleungnung. [After the denial], 11-verso
    - [Expulsion of merchants], 12
    - Passionsspiele O. - Ammergau 1922. Nr. 58 Vertreibung der H ndler. [Explulsion of Merchants], 12-verso
  - Oberammergau, Germany, circa 1922; 13 (Box 1600)
    - [Oberammergau and Laber mountains in background], 1
    - K nstlerkart von V. Marschall. [Artist Card by V. Marschall] Oberammergau gegen Osten, mit dem Laber (1683 m). [Oberammergau to the east, with the Laber mountains], 1-verso
    - [Oberammergau with the Passion Theater and the Laber mountains], 2
    - K nstlerkart von V. Marschall. [Artist Card by V. Marschall]Oberannergau mit dem Passionstheater und dem Laber (1683 m). [Oberammergau with the Passion Theater and the Laber mountains], 2-verso
    - Vila Krach. Pension Krach-Schilcher. Gru aus Oberammergau. [Greetings from Oberammergau] Fran Therese Reuten Renhulaerstraust 3/II. L. M nchen., 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - Vila Krach. Pension Krach-Schilcher. Gru aus Oberammergau. [Greetings from Oberammergau], 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
    - Vila Krach. Pension Krach-Schilcher. Gru aus Oberammergau. [Greetings from Oberammergau], 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
    - Vila Krach. Pension Krach-Schilcher. Gru aus Oberammergau. [Greetings from Oberammergau], 6
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 6-verso
  - India, circa 1922; 14 (Box 1600)
    - The Baby and his Goat, Jaipur., 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
  - Florence, Italy, circa 1922; 15 (Box 1600)
    - Firenze-Il Fiume Arno e Ponte S. Trinita [Florence-The Arno River and the Holy Trinity Bridge], 1
    - Florence was originally situated on the right bank of the Arno only, but it extended at an early period in the middle ages to the opposite bank. The Ponte Sta. Trinita was erected in 1252 and rebuilt in 1567 by Bartolomeo Ammanati, restored and widened in 1867. It is adorned with allegorical statues of the seasons., 1-verso
    - Firenze dalla via Barbacana [Florence seen from Via Barbacane], 2
    - Florence seen from Via Barbacan. Who can describe the charm of this pearl of Tuscany, surrounded by beautiful gardens on lovely hills! From such an enchanting spot you may have a wonderful view all over the town, with its fine buildings and the river Arno, which you will never forget., 2-verso
    - Firenze dal Giardino di Boboli [Florence from the Boboli Gardens], 3
    - The views of Florence from the Garden of Boboli are very enchanting. The towers and palaces, the dome and campanile of the Cathedral, form a charming picture and the long walks borderned with evergreens, adorned with statues, attract crowds of pleasure-seekers on Sundays., 3-verso
    - [Portrait of Dante], 4
    - Ritratto di Dante; Firenze [Portrait of Dante], 4-verso